ssh.com 2002-10-13

# SSH - Company Info

### SSH'S PRIVACY POLICY

The business of SSH Communications Security ("SSH") is security. For us security enables totally new ways of working together by bringing trust to communication. Trust is the ultimate key to fundamentally open and flexible interaction. We feel that protection of privacy is an inherent part of any policy aiming at creation of such trust. 

Below you will find information explaining our policy regarding collection, use and protection of personal information supplied to us when visiting this web site ("Website"). 

#### COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may access most areas of this Website without registration and without giving any personal information of yourself such as your name, address, phone number and e-mail address ("Personal Information"). 

However, in some circumstances you may be asked to provide us with Personal Information. Your Personal Information is mainly needed or used for the following purposes: 

  * To provide you with customized service and contents; 
  * To inform you of product upgrades, updated information on this Website and/or new offers and services of SSH; 
  * To identify you as the purchaser or the person downloading software from this Website. 

#### COLLECTING DOMAIN NAME AND IP ADDRESS INFORMATION

SSH collects domain-names and/or IP addresses which are used when accessing this Website. Domain-names and/or IP addresses are collected for system analysis and internal tracking purposes only. Collecting will occur automatically when you visit this Website without requiring any action on your part. 

#### COOKIES

Cookies are small files that a web site places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Some pages of this Website use cookies. SSH uses cookies generally in the technical implementation of the order process of software and for the purpose of providing you with customized information from this Website. SSH does not use cookies for reading data from your computer. Some browsers can be set to alert you when you are receiving a cookie and to give you the choice to accept or reject the cookie. If you choose not to accept a cookie from this Website some pages of this Website may not function properly and you may not be able to order or download software from this Website. 

#### DISCLOSURE

SSH uses its best efforts to protect Personal Information against loss and unauthorized use. Further, SSH will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties excluding, however, SSH's subsidiaries to the extent permitted by applicable law. 

#### UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

In the event your Personal Information has changed, for instance if you have a new address, you are encouraged to contact SSH through E-mail ([webmaster@ssh.com](mailto:webmaster@ssh.com)) and inform SSH about the changes. You may contact SSH any time through the above E-mail address to verify that your Personal Information is up to date and accurate. 

SSH reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any accessing of this Website signifies that you agree to SSH's Privacy Policy current at that date. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact SSH at [webmaster@ssh.com](mailto:webmaster@ssh.com). 

COPYRIGHT NOTICE 

Copyright © 2000 SSH Communications Security Ltd. All rights reserved. 

Home _:_ Products _:_ FAQ's _:_ Partners _:_ Tech _:_ Support  
Company _:_ Download _:_ Sales _:_ Contact info _:_ Feedback  
Terms and Conditions of Use _:_ Privacy Policy

Copyright © 2002 SSH Communications Security - All Rights Reserved
